[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 25, "question": "I mean, in the case of Arnold Schwarzenegger, do you think if the electorate had known that he had a love child by his housekeeper he would have ever become governor of California?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 26, "answer": "Well, I don't know the answer to that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Arnold Schwarzenegger"], "LOCATION": ["California"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 40, "question": "And were you aware of what transpired from January?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 41, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["January"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["David Axelrod", "Arnold Schwarzenegger"]}, "docId": "110517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "IN", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 48, "question": "Do you think that Arnold Schwarzenegger would have been able to become governor of California if this story had emerged before the election?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 49, "answer": "Well, I think -- David Axelrod is right, that clearly Arnold Schwarzenegger didn't think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Arnold Schwarzenegger"], "LOCATION": ["California"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "JJR", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "POS", "NNS", "CC", "WRB", "NNS", "POS", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 61, "question": "As a traditional sex scandal, should we all just grow up a bit and accept that, you know, people will misbehave sexually and it shouldn't have any effect on their work as politicians or as leaders of banks or whatever it may be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBP", "RP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VB", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 62, "answer": "Well, I think from public figures and politicians we do expect more, particularly because they actually vote on issues of morality and intrusions into people's lives and how people's lives are conducted.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBP", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 82, "question": "Should it matter politically?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 83, "answer": "Well, whether it should or it does are two different things.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 99, "question": "Why is that a surprise to anybody?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 100, "answer": "Well, because --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 140, "question": "Don't you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 141, "answer": "Yes, of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 153, "question": "Could we potentially see a movie version of Tiger Woods unfold?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 154, "answer": "Well, here's the sad part.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Tiger Woods"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 168, "question": "What's going on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 169, "answer": "Well, you know, if we're looking for moral leadership from our sports figures, from our entertainer, now from our politicians and businessmen, I think we're all looking in the wrong place.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "IN", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 185, "question": "What was your response to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 186, "answer": "Well, I think actually we've seen -- we see more of a divergence right now, that you can get away with it in sports and in entertainment and other places.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "POS", "JJ", "DT", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 212, "question": "Would you take on Dominique Strauss-Khan?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 213, "answer": "Well, let's separate the two.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dominique Strauss-Khan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "RB", "VB", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 260, "question": "Is this fair or is it prejudicial?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 261, "answer": "I think the only legitimate question for people to really complain about is the perp walk.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 264, "question": "And what do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 265, "answer": "Look, I think that it's probably not necessary.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 300, "question": "Can we expect any privacy anymore given the existence of Twitter, social networks, Facebook and so on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 301, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 308, "question": "How do you see the legal position in relation to this IMF chief going?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 309, "answer": "I think that the first question is going to be, is he going to get bail.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["IMF"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ":", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "DT", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 345, "question": "What do you make of this whole issue?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 346, "answer": "Well, I think that you -- first of all, these are always stunning developments when you hear them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "CC", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "CC", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 348, "question": "Should we?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 349, "answer": "And -- well, I think they're all human beings, and some -- you know, are flawed, and so, you know, I think that we should -- we should put our faith in them to the degree that we know what their public positions have been, what they've done with their -- but I think it's hard to get to know people.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 352, "question": "I mean, in the case of Arnold Schwarzenegger, do you think if the electorate had known that he had a love child by his housekeeper he would ever have become governor of California?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 353, "answer": "Well, I don't know the answer to that, but I suspect the fact that it didn't become public until after suggests that he didn't necessarily believe that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Arnold Schwarzenegger"], "LOCATION": ["California"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"]}, "docId": "110517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "WRB", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 355, "question": "When you see this -- you know, almost apocalyptic series of events we've had in the world with the Middle East uprisings, with what happened in Japan, with the killing of Osama bin Laden and so on, have you missed being back in the center of things at the White House, or are you still quietly there on the end of the phone?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNS", ",", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "EX", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 356, "answer": "Well, you know, look, there's no place like the White House when things are happening.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"], "LOCATION": ["Middle East", "Japan", "Osama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 362, "question": "Is it good or the bad to have -- be seeing more of him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "TO", "VB", ":", "VB", "VBG", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 363, "answer": "It's excellent.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["November of 2012"], "ORGANIZATION": ["Piers", "White House"]}, "docId": "110517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "EX", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "CC", "NNP", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 367, "question": "I mean in terms of the politics of what's been happening, how significant do you think, particularly the bin Laden incident, may have been for the Obama election campaign that will be coming up to?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBN", "VBG", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NN", ",", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "RP", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 368, "answer": "You know, Piers, I've been asked that question a lot, and I think it's very -- one thing you're acutely aware of when you're in the White House is that there are going to be a million developments between now and November of 2012.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "IN", "RB", "RB", "WDT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "JJ", ":", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 408, "question": "Watching Lauren go through that seizure?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 409, "answer": "Going through not just that seizure, but she had multiple, multiple -- dozens of seizures every single day.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 415, "question": "It's terrifying for new parents?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 416, "answer": "Totally terrifying.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 442, "question": "Why is that, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 443, "answer": "Well, I think a number of reasons.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", ":", "CC", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "VBG", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "JJR", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 476, "question": "What are the most effective ways we can try and change this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CC", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 477, "answer": "Well, I think one thing that we can do is just really -- and one of the things we've been successful at doing is changing the focus of research, which was always about sort of slapping more medications on seizures and hoping that you could just make them sort of subside.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 485, "question": "What a moment for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 486, "answer": "We still have no idea why that drug is working.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ":"], "qSentId": 489, "question": "And do you know how many other people it works on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 490, "answer": "It's --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 498, "question": "It was for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 499, "answer": "And we need to understand that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 515, "question": "Do you feel, Susan, that you've -- you've lost a life with Lauren, although she's alive and she's doing better than she was, that she's never going to lead the life that you would have hoped for when she was first born as a healthy baby?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 516, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Susan", "Lauren"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", ",", "IN", ":", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 522, "question": "Does she?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 523, "answer": "I just have to put it somewhere where I, you know -- I don't deal with it very well, because -- because it will get me pretty emotional.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["two percent"]}, "docId": "110517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "CD", "TO", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 545, "question": "Susan, how prevalent is epilepsy in America at the moment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 546, "answer": "You know, epilepsy affects one to two percent of the population worldwide.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 564, "question": "What impact did it have on you financially?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 565, "answer": "Well, there are all kinds of impacts on the family, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBP", ":", "IN", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", ":"], "qSentId": 584, "question": "If they're watching this and they either know people with epilepsy or they just want to help, what is the most effective way they can do this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 585, "answer": "Well, they can certainly join some of the events that we're having around the country that are -- are cropping up in places that other family members --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 586, "question": "You have a website?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 587, "answer": "We have a website, cureepilepsy.org.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", ":", "RB", ",", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 600, "question": "Has the government been doing enough in terms of providing funding for epilepsy research?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 601, "answer": "No, I -- well, look, I believe that medical research generally needs more.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 613, "question": "Put a little pressure on them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VB", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 614, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", ":"], "qSentId": 627, "question": "Where would the ticks be and where would the crosses be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "DT", "NNS", "VB", "CC", "WRB", "MD", "DT", "NNS", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 628, "answer": "Well, first of all, one of the reasons why we have a trusting relationship is because I reserve those kinds of comments --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 669, "question": "Presumably, you will be involved, as you were last time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 670, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CD", "NNS", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 671, "question": "Is the apparent chaos of the GOP at the moment an encouraging sign for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 672, "answer": "Well, look, you know, 16 months is an eternity in politics.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["GOP"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 676, "question": "Are you a betting man?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 677, "answer": "Not really --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 678, "question": "An occasional dabble?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 679, "answer": "Occasional.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 680, "question": "If you were about to put a little bet on it, who would you think may end up, as things stand, with the Republican nomination?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "MD", "VB", "RP", ",", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 681, "answer": "You know, I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 691, "question": "But as -- as things stand, it's looking pretty good for the president, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", ":", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 692, "answer": "Well --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110517pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 693, "question": "Been a good few weeks?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 694, "answer": "Well, I think we take it day by day.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]